{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622696","name":"Kiesling","address":"449 E Milwaukee Ave","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Kiesling LLC (Carlo Liburdi)","licenseNumber":"226541","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365","coords":"-83.06705,42.37134","geojson":{"id":"51622696","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.067051505,42.371338952]},"properties":{"name":"Kiesling","owner":"Kiesling LLC (Carlo Liburdi)","address":"449 E Milwaukee Ave","zipcode":"48202","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"226541","establishmentid":"51622696","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365","most_recent_license_date":"9/9/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622949","name":"Upfront Hospitality LLC dba Oak and Reel","address":"2921 E Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"785","name":"Parks Old Style Bar-B-Q ","address":"7444 Beaubien St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4173","name":"Hastings Street Ballroom & DBA Tangent G","address":"715 E Milwaukee Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"3608","name":"Firewater Bar & Grill II","address":"107 E Milwaukee Ave.  ","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4811","name":"Bucharest Grill Piquette","address":"110 Piquette Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"786","name":"Z's Villa","address":"42 Piquette Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"529","name":"Woodward Cocktail Bar","address":"6426 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"5183","name":"Atomic Chicken","address":"6500 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622897","name":"Yum Village LLC","address":"6500 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2153","name":"White Castle #44","address":"6364 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"52669","inspectionDate":"2020-09-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With ledges, projections, or crevices","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-102.20","violationDescription":"A PERSON IN CHARGE who demonstrates knowledge by being a FOOD protection manager that is certified by a FOOD protection manager certification program that is evaluated and listed by a Conference for Food Protection-recognized accrediting agency as conforming to the Conference for Food Protection Standards for Accreditation of Food Protection Manager Certification Programs is deemed to comply with Â¶ 2-102.11(B).","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food Protection Manager","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48964","inspectionDate":"2019-08-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing lavatories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Inadequate","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.115","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, live animals may not be allowed on the PREMISES of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pet(s)","subItem":"dogs","problemDescription":"Present in dining area","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-501.115","violationDescription":"A storage area and enclosure for REFUSE, recyclables, or returnables shall be maintained free of unnecessary items, and clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Refuse storage area(s)/enclosures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"OUTSIDE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-09T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43045","inspectionDate":"2018-07-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"quaternary ammonia","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"In the Bulk food bins","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622696"}}